https://www.morselawoffice.com/privacy-policy/

Call Now To See How We Can Help!HomeAbout UsFirm OverviewAbout AttorneyPractice AreasERISAAn OverviewDisability and RetirementLong-Term DisabilityFamily LawAn OverviewDivorceChild Custody & Child SupportProperty Division & AlimonyPost-Divorce EnforcementTaking Your Case To Family CourtPersonal InjuryAn OverviewCar AccidentConstruction AccidentsMedical MalpracticeOther CasesBusiness And Commercial LawAnimal Rights litigationTestimonialsClient TestimonialsAttorney EndorsementsBlogCase SummaryFAQsPersonal Injury FAQsCar Accident FAQsTruck Accident FAQsMotorcycle Accident FAQsContact UsOffice LocationMenu HomeAbout UsFirm OverviewAbout AttorneyPractice AreasERISAAn OverviewDisability and RetirementLong-Term DisabilityFamily LawAn OverviewDivorceChild Custody & Child SupportProperty Division & AlimonyPost-Divorce EnforcementTaking Your Case To Family CourtPersonal InjuryAn OverviewCar AccidentConstruction AccidentsMedical MalpracticeOther CasesBusiness And Commercial LawAnimal Rights litigationTestimonialsClient TestimonialsAttorney EndorsementsBlogCase SummaryFAQsPersonal Injury FAQsCar Accident FAQsTruck Accident FAQsMotorcycle Accident FAQsContact UsOffice Location Privacy PolicyThe website for the Law Office of Mark B. Morse, LLC, www.morselawoffice.com, collects information of a personal nature, such as names and email addresses, when our users voluntarily submit this information. We use this information for the purpose of contacting potential clients to schedule an initial consultation. Our law firm does not sell any of this personal information to third parties; it is used for our own purposes only. Our website also collects technical information such as IP addresses and dates and times of access. We use this information to analyze trends and improve our website’s performance. This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.Some of the pages on this site link to external websites. These hyperlinks are included solely as a convenience to our users and do not imply any responsibility for the linked site or its contents. We encourage our users to be aware when they have left our website. Any browsing on an external site is governed by that site’s privacy policy, which may differ from our own policy.If you have any questions about our firm or our policies, contact us. GET HELP NOWHome » Privacy Policy
Office LocationThe Law Office Of Mark B. Morse LLC
420 Angell Street Suite 2
Providence, RI 02906
Phone: (401) 831-0555
Fax: (401) 273-0937 A Lawyer You Can Talk To
On Social Media Subscribe To Our Monthly NewsletterPlease provide your name and email address to subscribe to our monthly newsletter.
SubmitHomeAbout AttorneyPersonal InjuryERISABlogCommunity ServiceContact UsCopyright©2020, The Law Office Of Mark B. Morse LLC. All Rights Reserved.
